techmediaguide.com 2018-01-28

# Privacy policy - Techmediaguide - Latest technology updates on Social media , Marketing

## PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: 26 August 2017  
This privacy policy explains how Industry Dive Inc. (“we,” “us,” “our”), affiliates, and subsidiaries, will collect, use, and share the information that you provide to us through your use of our mobile applications and websites that link to this privacy policy (collectively, our “Properties”). Below is a summary of the key provisions in our privacy policy. We encourage you to read the full privacy policy to understand our information practices.

We may share personal information that we collect with third parties for their direct marketing or other purposes, with affiliates and service providers that help us operate our business, to comply with the law or to respond to legal inquiries, as part of a corporate change like an acquisition or merger, and in other cases. To learn more about how we share your information and the choices you have, please click here.

We may permit third-party services to collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites including to provide more relevant ads to you across the Internet. To learn more about this practice and the choices that you can make, please click here.

 **Personal Information**

When accessing our Properties, you may voluntarily provide personal information during your visit or by contacting us. We may collect this information when you visit our site to read or download information, as well as when you sign up for our newsletters. We may also receive personal information about you from third parties, such as partners, affiliates, service providers, and subsidiaries. We may combine this information with the information that you provide to us.

 **Non-Personal Information**

When you use our Properties we may collect various non-personal information, including, but not limited to, the date and time you access our Properties, the website from which you linked to our Property, IP address, your operating system and browser type, and your mobile device. Such information is used for a variety of purposes such as operating and improving our Properties, analyzing demographic and statistical research about website usage, customizing offers, and to monitor the Properties for compliance with our terms of service and the law, as well as other purposes.

 **Location Information**

We may also collect geolocation data pertaining to your mobile device, which may be linked to a device identifier or IP address. We may use this information to provide our services to you and to provide more relevant advertising content to you on our Properties. If you do not want to provide your location to us, please use the settings available on your mobile device to limit this sharing. Please note that if you limit sharing of geolocation data, certain features of the mobile application may not work.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

Tech Media Guide can update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
